Erick Mancia

4250 S Jones Blvd. Las vegas NV, 89103 emancia35@gmail.com 410-9342686

Career Highlight:

4 years of experience like a restaurant waiter in Maryland,

14 years of experience in Walmart for different areas as Logistic, Marketing, Regional information, Support Applications by Mexico and Central America. Detail:

6 years of experience as Team Leader role for Business Intelligence and Reporting by Walmart. Countries Guatemala, Costa Rica, El Salvador, Mexico.

4 years of experience like a Regional Pricing Analyst. Country El Salvador.

4 years of experience like a supply chain management at Walmart Cascadas Warehouse. Country El Salvador. Driving inventory over 15 MM.

WORK EXPERIENCE

(Maryland, USA- Restaurant Experience)

Feb. 2017 – To date. Restaurant Waiter, Busser, Cook. Primary point contact with customers, hospitality and ensuring the dining experience.

(Mexico – Mexico City)

Nov 2013 – Nov 2016. Application support Business Intelligence: Credit Card System (cards Issues, method of payment). Dot net support, ETL process, offshore coordinator.

Walmart Mexico and Central America. (From Jan. 2002 To Nov. 2013)

Dec 2010 – OCT 2013. Business Intelligence Coordinator: ETL monitoring and support application over all projects related to Marketing, Finances, Logistic.

Apr 2006 – Nov 2010. Pricing Analyst: Approach to evaluate product options when possible. With this approach, the prices of provider's products is compared against competing alternatives or substitutes.

EDUCATION

[2012] [Bachelor degree in Computer Science. University of Technology. (UTEC) SLV]

[2011] [Specialization Implementation of Data Mining. University of Technology. (UTEC) SLV]

[2015] [Project Manager Specialization: University of Salamanca (Spain)]

[2016] [R Programming: Johns Hopkins University (USA)]

REFERENCES

Nelson Mendez Campos No:(506) 258-28451 Email: Nelson.Mendez@walmart.com Jorge Gutierrez Avedano No: (52) 0445512463592 – Jorge.gutierrez.avendano@ibm.com Edgar Martinez No: (52) 5551079204 Email: Edgar.martinez@capgemini.com